# Fatemeh RasolZadeh | Frontend Developer

Tehran, Iran | Linkedin | Github | Gmail | +98 919 792 2488

## Summery

I am a frontend developer with over two years of experience. I started coding in 2021, working on diverse projects with an agile team at ASP. After that, in 2022, I have decided to join Datsa for more significant challenges and responsibilities. I am seeking roles that offer challenging opportunities and allow me to push my limits. I thrive in challenging environments where I can continuously learn and grow, utilizing my skills to overcome obstacles and achieve exceptional results.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Datsa, Tehran** – Frontend developer

Nov 2022 - present (1 yr and 4 mos)

- Developed and maintained best-practice code in different applications such as admin panel and customer
  portal for a multinational trading company both for operator and customer side. Collaborate with back-end,
  front-end developers and designers in large-scale projects.
- Planning the project structure with typescript and using RTK Query for fetch and caching data. Build forms with the latest packages such as Formik and YUP for form validation.
- We build a dashboard for drivers as a product that helps users browse through tons of routes and customize routes to match their needs, Find the latitude and longitude of a customer address, and also create a polygon for each zone using react leaflet.

### **Aseman Sooye Parsian, Tehran** – Frontend developer

July 2021 - Nov 2022 (1 yr and 5 mos)

- Developed an admin panel using React, Redux for state management, RESTful API for data fetching, and Material UI for design. This resulted in improved performance for branch operators.
- Built complex processes such as ordering, account management, reports, package tracking and their location. Implement data illustration with different types of charts and bars for reports. Using React Webcam for Records customer videos, pictures, and track products. We used a socket connection to track and record real-time data between our client-side and application
- Created a customer portal using Next.js and Redux Toolkit for state management. Utilized Tailwind CSS to
  ensure a responsive and user-friendly interface. Implemented order tracking functionality and used graphql
  to fetch, cache, and modify application data with the Apollo client library.

#### Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJs, Redux, NextJs, MaterialUi, Ant design, Tailwind, RESTful API, GraphQL, git, Agile methodology, scram

#### **EDUCATION**

**Islamic Azad University, Hashtgerd Branch, Karaj** - Bachelor of Science in computer engineering (OCtober 2019 - present, Karaj)